nshss.org 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy National Society of High School Scholars

This is the web site of **The National Society of High School Scholars**.

Our postal address is:  
 **International Headquarters  
1936 North Druid Hills Road   
Atlanta, Georgia  30319**

We can be reached via e-mail at support@nshss.org or you can reach us by telephone at 404-235-5500 or 1-866-343-1800.

The National Society of High School Scholars (“NSHSS”) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”).

NSHSS is an international organization dedicated to recognizing and supporting academic excellence with the overarching goal of bettering the world through helping young people. NSHSS values its members and their concerns about privacy. To this end, NSHSS engages in consistent information practices and uses its best efforts to make clear disclosures regarding those practices. This Privacy Policy is a part of that effort.

In general, NSHSS does not share your personally identifying information with third parties unless you permit it.

_What does this Privacy Policy cover?_  

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, storage, and disclosure of your information by NSHSS. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We will clearly disclose any exceptions to the Privacy Policy prior to collecting any information from our users.

NSHSS may decide to modify or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post any changes or new language here.

_What information does NSHSS collect?_

NSHSS may collect contact information including your name, address, e-mail address, and other personally identifying information.  We collect this information when you become a member of NSHSS; place orders for products; register for seminars or other events; request information from us; or submit information through our website.

_What does NSHSS do with the information it collects?_

When you make a purchase from us, your contact information may be used by NSHSS or shared with third parties for the purposes of processing your transaction, including fraud prevention and credit card authorization.  Additionally, NSHSS may use contact information to notify you about new products, promotions, and special offers from NSHSS or our partners that will benefit you.  If you are not interested in receiving this information, please email us at remove@nshss.org and we will remove your name from our mailing lists.

_Is data stored by NSHSS secure?_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, NSHSS has physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online.

_How do I find out more about NSHSS's information practices?_

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy, or about our collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact NSHSS as follows:

NSHSS   
International Headquarters  
1936 North Druid Hills Rd.   
Atlanta, GA 30319  
E-mail: support@nshss.org

This Privacy Policy was last revised on June 2, 2014.
